A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Associate Vice President for Administration, Fairfield Osborn Lectures FA225
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Associate Vice President for Administration, Fairfield Osborn Lectures
1970, 1972-1974, 1978-1986
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
FA225
0.44 Cubic Feet
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Though these materials originate from the office of Cynthia Greenleaf, Associate Vice President for Administration, they predate the 1988 creation of the office.
Scope and Contents note
Includes correspondence, memoranda, clippings, lists of attendees, news releases, pamphlets/brochures, lecture invitations, announcements, and tickets.
Arrangement note
Arranged in chronological order.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 395-1
Conditions Governing Access note
Collection is open for scholarly research.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment. Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Medical education; Medical sciences; Medical research; Life sciences; Rockefeller University
- Frank Fraser-Darling Lecture, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Clifton Wharton Lecture, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Maurice Strong Lecture, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Maurice Strong Lecture, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- John Stevenson Lecture, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Russell Peterson Lecture, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Prince Philip Lecture, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- A.W. Clausen Lecture, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Carl Djerassi Lecture, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Archie Carr Lecture, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Conservation 2100, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)